{"sid": "I07NVEAUB6C8_main", "calc_equals_delay": 5, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 2227146, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 2227148, "question": "7+3+7+68", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["calc_6", 2231336], ["calc_8", 2231908], ["calc_+", 2232780], ["calc_7", 2233481], ["calc_=", 2234304], ["submit", 2242628]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "285", "answered_time": 2242628, "user_answer": "85", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "285", "question_time_start": 2242629, "question": "3+44+28", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["calc_2", 2247526], ["calc_8", 2248477], ["calc_+", 2249145], ["calc_4", 2249910], ["calc_4", 2250146], ["calc_=", 2251060], ["submit", 2258722]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "269", "answered_time": 2258722, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "269", "question_time_start": 2258722, "question": "3+79+88", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["calc_7", 2260749], ["calc_9", 2261318], ["calc_+", 2263293], ["calc_8", 2263981], ["calc_8", 2264158], ["calc_=", 2264917], ["submit", 2271892]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "256", "answered_time": 2271892, "user_answer": "170", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "256", "question_time_start": 2271892, "question": "4+3+8+98", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["submit", 2278879]], "time_left_end": "249", "answered_time": 2278879, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "249", "question_time_start": 2278879, "question": "76+47", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["submit", 2282530]], "time_left_end": "246", "answered_time": 2282530, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "246", "question_time_start": 2282530, "question": "9+3+13", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 2285977]], "time_left_end": "242", "answered_time": 2285977, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "242", "question_time_start": 2285977, "question": "3+7+4+24", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 2289230]], "time_left_end": "239", "answered_time": 2289230, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "239", "question_time_start": 2289230, "question": "16+786", "correct_answer": 802, "events": [["submit", 2297297]], "time_left_end": "231", "answered_time": 2297297, "user_answer": "802", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "231", "question_time_start": 2297298, "question": "23+37", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 2300128]], "time_left_end": "228", "answered_time": 2300128, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "228", "question_time_start": 2300129, "question": "4+9+27", "correct_answer": 40, "events": [["submit", 2304854]], "time_left_end": "223", "answered_time": 2304854, "user_answer": "40", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 2304854, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "223", "question_time_start": 2304854, "question": "76+29", "correct_answer": 105, "events": [["submit", 2309845]], "time_left_end": "218", "answered_time": 2309845, "user_answer": "105", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "218", "question_time_start": 2309846, "question": "7+8+9+89", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["submit", 2320697]], "time_left_end": "207", "answered_time": 2320697, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "False", "score": "10"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "207", "question_time_start": 2320697, "question": "96+17", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["submit", 2325649]], "time_left_end": "202", "answered_time": 2325649, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "202", "question_time_start": 2325649, "question": "54+424", "correct_answer": 478, "events": [["submit", 2331348]], "time_left_end": "197", "answered_time": 2331348, "user_answer": "478", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "197", "question_time_start": 2331348, "question": "4+7+8+79", "correct_answer": 98, "events": [["calc_1", 2337365], ["calc_9", 2338120], ["calc_+", 2338701], ["calc_7", 2339674], ["calc_9", 2340333], ["calc_=", 2341189], ["submit", 2348233]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "180", "answered_time": 2348233, "user_answer": "98", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "180", "question_time_start": 2348233, "question": "3+26+84", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["calc_2", 2353096], ["calc_9", 2353993], ["calc_+", 2354864], ["calc_8", 2355470], ["calc_4", 2356034], ["calc_=", 2356735], ["submit", 2363484]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "165", "answered_time": 2363484, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "165", "question_time_start": 2363485, "question": "6+86+48", "correct_answer": 140, "events": [["calc_8", 2365349], ["calc_6", 2365896], ["calc_+", 2366469], ["calc_4", 2367485], ["calc_8", 2368472], ["calc_=", 2369539], ["submit", 2376736]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "151", "answered_time": 2376736, "user_answer": "140", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "151", "question_time_start": 2376736, "question": "6+4+17", "correct_answer": 27, "events": [["submit", 2379553]], "time_left_end": "149", "answered_time": 2379553, "user_answer": "27", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "149", "question_time_start": 2379554, "question": "9+7+9+37", "correct_answer": 62, "events": [["submit", 2387471]], "time_left_end": "141", "answered_time": 2387471, "user_answer": "62", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "141", "question_time_start": 2387471, "question": "8+7+44", "correct_answer": 59, "events": [["submit", 2391201]], "time_left_end": "137", "answered_time": 2391201, "user_answer": "59", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 2391201, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "137", "question_time_start": 2391201, "question": "8+9+23", "correct_answer": 40, "events": [["submit", 2394972]], "time_left_end": "133", "answered_time": 2394972, "user_answer": "40", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "133", "question_time_start": 2394973, "question": "96+28", "correct_answer": 124, "events": [["submit", 2400202]], "time_left_end": "128", "answered_time": 2400202, "user_answer": "124", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "128", "question_time_start": 2400203, "question": "4+3+9+74", "correct_answer": 90, "events": [["submit", 2406336]], "time_left_end": "122", "answered_time": 2406336, "user_answer": "90", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "122", "question_time_start": 2406336, "question": "28+83", "correct_answer": 111, "events": [["submit", 2409653]], "time_left_end": "119", "answered_time": 2409653, "user_answer": "111", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "119", "question_time_start": 2409653, "question": "8+64+18", "correct_answer": 90, "events": [["submit", 2417804]], "time_left_end": "111", "answered_time": 2417804, "user_answer": "90", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "111", "question_time_start": 2417804, "question": "7+49+33", "correct_answer": 89, "events": [["submit", 2421556]], "time_left_end": "107", "answered_time": 2421556, "user_answer": "89", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "107", "question_time_start": 2421556, "question": "97+124", "correct_answer": 221, "events": [["submit", 2429255]], "time_left_end": "99", "answered_time": 2429255, "user_answer": "221", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "99", "question_time_start": 2429255, "question": "9+8+7+28", "correct_answer": 52, "events": [["calc_1", 2436263], ["calc_5", 2436838], ["calc_+", 2438131], ["calc_3", 2439895], ["calc_7", 2440607], ["calc_=", 2441308], ["submit", 2447523]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "81", "answered_time": 2447523, "user_answer": "52", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "81", "question_time_start": 2447524, "question": "9+8+9+38", "correct_answer": 64, "events": [["submit", 2464806]], "time_left_end": "64", "answered_time": 2464806, "user_answer": "64", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "64", "question_time_start": 2464807, "question": "7+6+17", "correct_answer": 30, "events": [["submit", 2468139]], "time_left_end": "60", "answered_time": 2468139, "user_answer": "30", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 2468139, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "60", "question_time_start": 2468139, "question": "6+3+27", "correct_answer": 36, "events": [["submit", 2471641]], "time_left_end": "57", "answered_time": 2471641, "user_answer": "36", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "57", "question_time_start": 2471641, "question": "8+4+4+57", "correct_answer": 73, "events": [["submit", 2477445]], "time_left_end": "51", "answered_time": 2477445, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "False", "score": "28"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "51", "question_time_start": 2477445, "question": "3+3+3+69", "correct_answer": 78, "events": [["submit", 2486647]], "time_left_end": "42", "answered_time": 2486647, "user_answer": "78", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "42", "question_time_start": 2486647, "question": "4+67+58", "correct_answer": 129, "events": [["calc_6", 2492129], ["calc_7", 2492919], ["calc_+", 2493811], ["calc_6", 2494594], ["calc_2", 2495180], ["calc_=", 2495961], ["submit", 2497774]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "31", "answered_time": 2497774, "user_answer": "129", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "31", "question_time_start": 2497775, "question": "33+86", "correct_answer": 119, "events": [["submit", 2500725]], "time_left_end": "28", "answered_time": 2500725, "user_answer": "119", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "28", "question_time_start": 2500725, "question": "4+43+34", "correct_answer": 81, "events": [["submit", 2506992]], "time_left_end": "22", "answered_time": 2506992, "user_answer": "81", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "22", "question_time_start": 2506992, "question": "6+4+6+47", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 2512149]], "time_left_end": "16", "answered_time": 2512149, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "33"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "16", "question_time_start": 2512150, "question": "36+814", "correct_answer": 850, "events": [["submit", 2518403]], "time_left_end": "10", "answered_time": 2518403, "user_answer": "850", "user_correct": "True", "score": "34"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "10", "question_time_start": 2518403, "question": "57+87", "correct_answer": 144, "events": [["submit", 2521513]], "time_left_end": "7", "answered_time": 2521513, "user_answer": "144", "user_correct": "True", "score": "35"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "7", "question_time_start": 2521514, "question": "3+4+43", "correct_answer": 50, "events": [["submit", 2524410]], "time_left_end": "4", "answered_time": 2524410, "user_answer": "50", "user_correct": "True", "score": "36"}}}, "block_4": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 2524410, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "4", "question_time_start": 2524410, "question": "3+28+99", "correct_answer": 130, "events": []}}}}}